WE ARE FIGHTING DREAMERS takami wo mezashite
we are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
FIGHTING DREAMERS narifuri kamawazu
Fighting Dreamers, don't care what people think about them
FIGHTING DREAMERS shinjiru ga mama ni
Fighting Dreamers, follow what they believe
OLI OLI OLI OH JUST GO MY WAY
oli oli oli oh just go my way
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase LIKE A dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN)
Right here right now (burn)
kewashii shura no michi no naka
down a difficult road filled with endless struggles
hito no chizu wo hirogete doko e yuku
where do you think you are going following someone else's map?
gokusaishoku no karasu ga sore wo ubaitotte yaburisuteta
an insightful crow comes along to tear up the map
saa kokoro no me mihiraite shika to ima wo mikiwamero (YEAH)
Now open your eyes and take a look at the truth (yeah)
ushinau mono nante nai sa iza mairou
there's nothing to lose, so let's go
WE ARE FIGHTING DREAMERS takami wo mezashite
we are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
FIGHTING DREAMERS narifuri kamawazu
Fighting Dreamers, don't care what people think about them
FIGHTING DREAMERS shinjiru ga mama ni
Fighting Dreamers, follow what they believe
OLI OLI OLI OH JUST GO MY WAY
oli oli oli oh! just go my way
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase LIKE A dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN) buttagitteku ze GET THE FIRE
right here right now (burn) let's slash right through and get the fire
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase Like a dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN) buttagitteku ze GET THE FIRE BANG
right here right now (burn) let's slash right through and get the fire, bang!
Sasuke-kun...
My, my arm!
Are you okay, Orochimaru-sama?
Please take this medicine quickly.
Oh, my...
Just as I get back,
I have to clean the room.
Please make sure to take
your medicine.
I don't need that kind
of lip service.
It's medicine that I prescribed.
The pain should subside
at least slightly.
The pain on this arm
that seems to burn...
I never thought that it causes
this much suffering.
Sarutobi... known as Third Hokage.
It's his last curse, after all.
Enough of the talking...
More importantly,
has that individual been found?
Yes... She seems to be at a place
called Tanzaku Town.
Tanzaku Town...
Is that so...?
But the opponent is one of the Sannin,
the Legendary Three Ninja.
It won't be that simple.
Good medicine tends to taste bitter.
Here.
It's the same one...
But this is the trick?
You're the type who was yelled at
at the academy
for not having concentration, right?
That doesn't have anything
to do with me now.
Look at this paper.
Uh?
I've seen it.
Fine, then.
Look at it again.
Hmm?
So what is this?
It's not something that
I need to explain in length,
but when you first looked
at this blank piece of paper,
you just glanced at
the whole thing, correct?
Probably.
Then where do you look on this one?
Most likely the point in the middle?
When a human being looks at
just a blank piece of paper,
he doesn't know where to look,
so the eyes wander.
But if you put even a single point on it,
the mind focuses there...
This is concentrating at a single point
and as you focus your mind,
you become spiritually stable and
you are able to extract unexpected power.
Huh?
When you opened a hole
on the rubber ball,
you must have been
concentrating desperately
to fill up the Chakra
in the palm of your hand.
Yeah, yeah.
When you concentrate,
power emerges.
But without a target,
it is difficult to concentrate.
That's why we have this...
Listen Naruto, from now on,
when you store up the Chakra
you build in your right hand,
try to store it up by concentrating
on that mark.
Concentrate...
All right, I'll try it!
The Leaf Village Mark
and
Forehead Protector
Concentrate!
Damn it. It's not supposed to be like this.
It has to break like "pang!".
Concentrate!
Hello... I'd like to make a little inquiry.
Damn it.
Concentrate.
Concentrate!
No good.
Damn it. What does it mean
to concentrate?!
Damn you, Sarutobi!
All right then...
I'm going again to gather
some information.
What...? But you just came.
I don't have any time to waste.
Hey, hey...!
Isn't there going to be even
a little soulful game of catch
between the master and pupil?
You scoundrel.
Strike!
Here, the game of catch is over.
See you later.
Humph... I'll forget about that Pervy Sage
and work hard by myself.
That's the only way, Naruto...
You have to do this training alone.
You have the ability to approach
the Fourth Hokage's level...
Grasp it by yourself!
Hmm... Never seen her.
If that's the case...
Sorry to bother you.
I know the person.
As well as where she is right now.
I'll buy you a drink.
There's no need.
I was able to win a tidy sum...
Thanks to that lady.
Yeah... you are indeed
the Legendary Sitting Duck.
She lost again, huh.
Her losses started to pile up...
So she was talking about
changing her location.
Where to?
One of the Sannin, Tsunade-sama,
is staying at Tanzaku Town over there.
Then this arm can finally...
Even if it's good medicine,
you won't get away with just
a bitter taste with that person.
It's fine.
Seven, seven, seven...
Here it comes!
Congratulations to the customer!
Fever has started
on machine number 44.
Now, please keep on getting it out
like a flood.
Tsunade-sama, a rare thing does happen
once in a while.
A 3-7 for me?
Oh wow, lady.
Yeah, what a great work.
Wish I could be favored
by good fortune too.
— Oh, here it comes again!
— Here it comes again!
Yay... it's "fever" again!
A person like me pulls
a big hit like this...
I have a bad premonition.
I also have some knowledge
regarding Tsunade-sama...
I did use to be part of
the Medical Corps, after all.
She was the first person to propose
what is now an accepted practice
of assigning one medical specialist
to a small squad of four.
This was a very revolutionary idea...
A small combat unit that doesn't
even have emergency medical skills,
what would happen to them in a battlefield
is clearer than seeing fire.
Countless experiences in war
simply became knowledge
to equip themselves with.
Many who were sacrificed
led to the creation of that style.
A person understands the nature
of things for the first time
after losing them.
And the thing created by
one of the legendary Sannin,
who is known as the medical specialist
is that sacrifice.
Not working...
I got to concentrate even more.
Concentrate, concentrate.
Concentrate!
Concentrate...
Concentrate on one point.
Strike!
That stupid perv's face floats up
in my head
and I can't even concentrate.
Oh boy...
Some gal somewhere is talking
about me again.
"Pinball Games"
Wait for me, Tsunade-sama!
What's the matter?
Your winning this much is like a miracle...
But you don't look pleased at all.
This town.
Huh?
I get a bad premonition.
We're going to hurry up and leave.
But this is a tourist resort...
We should take our time and
go see the famous castle and all.
Then we're going to hurry up
and see it so we can leave.
But... Tsunade-sama!
Orochimaru-sama!
Let's get this business over with.
Even if we have to use
a slightly rough method.
I got to do it.
Ouch!
Ouch... It hurts so much,
I can't even build up my Chakra...
He might be reaching his limit soon.
Just a bit... just a bit more rest.
Hey!
You guys, we're in class right now.
You... fools!
You guys have no concentration at all...!
This is not the way to
become fine Ninja.
How can we stay still at a table,
right, Akamaru?
I'm hungry.
Sensei, if it's a scolding,
do it quickly.
What the...?! You, you guys...
From now, we will have
an after-school lesson
to teach you guys more concentration!
— What?!
What's this?
You guys are going to do from now
what the predecessors of
the Leaf Village
used to perform every day
as a concentration method!
It is training to build up Chakra
by concentrating your entire energy
on the leaf on your forehead.
It's an ancient way of learning
how not to become distracted
from anything else
by concentrating on a single point,
the leaf.
The one who hones his concentration
is truly a great Ninja...
This is the origin of the Leaf Symbol
on the headband.
That sounds like a lie.
Aren't you making that story up
to force us to try harder?
I'm not making this up!
It's a true story.
Anyhow, can you really become
a great Ninja
by just polishing your concentration?
At any rate,
a great Ninja is a guy who's strong.
Hey, you have a point.
This stuff...
Bye, bye Sensei!
Hey, hey, you guys wait a minute.
— We won't wait!
— We don't have time for that!
Hey! You misfits!
This is the same thing.
I should have paid more attention
to what Iruka-sensei was saying...
I'm so stupid.
But nothing will start
if I just keep on regretting.
All right, I'm going to master this!
Concentrate, concentrate...
Concentrate!
Wow! Tanzaku Castle sure does have
a commanding presence!
It's worth being designated
as the cultural heritage.
Don't dally...
We're going to hurry up
and leave this town.
Tsunade-sama, please look more carefully...
It costs nothing to view.
Tsunade-sama?
What is this chill?
Now!
What a kid...
Raising the density in Chakra
to the point that it burns the palm.
He never ceases to amaze me.
It broke.
Good! The second step seems
to be complete.
Hurry... The third step.
That will come later.
We'll now go meet Tsunade.
That's...
Orochimaru.
I found you.
gaman no renzoku dattaro
a cycle of hardship, right?
kokoro de naiteita ndarou
inside, we were crying, right?
jibun de kimeta sono yume dake wa yuzurenai ndarou
but the one thing we won't give up is the dream we've chosen, right?
wakiyaku dakedo
it's a secondary role
kage no hito dakedo
a role in the shadows
yume to mukiau toki kurai
but in reaching for that dream
man naka ni isasete shoujiki ni isasete
let us stay centered, let us stay true
ima made nandomo nan toka akiramezu ni
over and over, we hung on without giving up
ima made nandomo tachi agatte kita janai ka
over and over, we kept coming back up
ima made nandomo
over and over, we believed and dreamed
bokura
nandomo
shinjite
yume mite nandomo
ima made nandomo baka o mite kita janai ka
over and over, we've seen fools
ima made nandomo hito no kage ni tatte kita janai ka
over and over, we've stood in the shadows of others
saa shuyaku da yo jibun no yume kurai wagamama de isasete
now, it's our turn... let us bask in our dreams
I can master the third step while walking?
Give me a break!
Fool! If we don't hurry it up,
we'll lose Tsunade!
Besides, she's short-tempered
and impatient!
Where are we heading?
If she's here in this town, we'll just
look for her from somewhere high up.
— So we'll climb up a castle.
— Castle?!
— Can't you see over there?!
— Which way is "over there"?
I'm saying...
Oh! What the...?!
Next time:
"Ripple."